<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[The Partially Unauthorized History of Jump, Little Children]]></title>
  <link href="http://jumplittlechildren.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://jumplittlechildren.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-05T10:53:31-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://jumplittlechildren.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Matthew Bivins]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Predictions]]></title>
    <link href="http://jumplittlechildren.github.io/blog/2014/03/03/my-first-nerdy-post/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-03T08:14:02-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://jumplittlechildren.github.io/blog/2014/03/03/my-first-nerdy-post</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When the band ended, there were two predictions made for what I was going to do after it was all over. That was such a time of wondering and worry: none of us had a clear idea exactly what we were going to do when the band ended. Well, maybe Ward did. He was going to write an album of country songs and maybe move to New York City. He did both things, bless his heart.</p>

<p>But the predictions: one, that Evan and I were going to become web designers. &ldquo;Build websites&rdquo; was the phrase then. And here we are, doing just that. That premonition was given to us by our manager John Caldwell. He is definitely one for knowing a little bit about the future.</p>

<p>The second one came from Jay Clifford. We were talking about the future and he suggested that I was going to be a writer. And more specifically that I was going to write down the history of Jump. At the time I scoffed at this idea, because I couldn&rsquo;t imagine a life that didn&rsquo;t involve being on stage all the time. But I&rsquo;ve had that life, since then, and I&rsquo;m not entirely sure I need that life right now. Perhaps Jay was right, and I&rsquo;m meant to chronicle those years, for posterity. For my own memory. It has been almost 10 years now since the band&rsquo;s last show, so it&rsquo;s not going to be easy, but I&rsquo;ll try and track down old &ldquo;journal&rdquo; posts and ask the other guys for specifics if I get stuck. I like the idea of this being a blog rather than a book, at least for now. Jump wasn&rsquo;t exactly a huge band. I&rsquo;m glad that we had the number of fans that we did, but I can&rsquo;t imagine people actually <em>looking</em> for a book about Jump, Little Children. A blog will do, Jay. But sure. I&rsquo;ll write it down.</p>

<p>The goal is to try and remember as much as I can about the history of the band. And to be as dead honest as I can be about what I do remember. There is no one to impress here, anymore; this is for me, and for anyone else interested, but I&rsquo;m not required to report the sunny side of everything as I did when I was writing about the band before. You have to, you know. You have to be happy even when times are tough. Times aren&rsquo;t always tough! But it&rsquo;s part of marketing. It&rsquo;ll be nice to be free of that marketing.</p>

<p>For those of you that were actually fans, there will be repeats of stories you might already know, and I may skip some parts that don&rsquo;t shine in my mind as brightly as others for writing down. For those of you that have never heard of Jump, Little Children, I&rsquo;m probably not going to spend much time on character descriptions or specifics of how the music sounded or where we traveled. If I get too far into feeling like I&rsquo;m telling a true story, I&rsquo;ll probably get bogged down and stop this when it gets to be too much work. I don&rsquo;t want that to happen; as I go along maybe I&rsquo;ll build some &ldquo;about this&rdquo; pages to do some back-story explaining but it might take a while. Again…this is for me, for the rest of the guys in the band, maybe. Do we deserve a biography? Maybe not, but a lot of this stuff was pretty fucking interesting, so it might be worth your time.</p>

<p>So! as they say: Once upon a time&hellip;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
